# **RIKKE BLOM THØGERSEN**



I specialise in online communication, and take pride in constructing well-produced written and visual texts. Over the last couple of years, layout, web development and graphic design have become some of my favorite genres.

I enjoy working in dynamic teams with room for both personal initiative and exchange of ideas.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Danish, native speaker English, fluent written & spoken German, beginner

# **CONTACT**



+45 28763312



rikke\_blom@hotmail.com



Peter Bangs Vej 161 2000 Frederiksberg

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2021-now	Campaign Specialist, Wunderman Thompson MAP    quality assurance    HTML emails    Adobe Campaign    Braze
2020	Student Assistant, KEA Facility     consumer behaviour    nudging    Microsoft Excel
2017	Communication Intern, Odense Municipality     SoMe    websites    graphic design    administration    newsletters
2012-2013	Pedagogical assistant, Assens Municipality
2008-2012	Sales Assistant, Tommerup Kiosk

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

2016-2019	Boardmember, Erasmus Student Network Odense Communication Manager & Secretary     SoMe    event planning    blogging    newsletters    photography    coordination of volunteers    minute taking    travel guide    administration
2015-2016	Active Member, Erasmus Student Network Odense     SoMe    event planning    blogging    newsletter    photography
2010-2016	Youth Camp coordinator, Cultural Village Tommerup - a part of Cultural Villages of Europe    recruitment of volunteers    coordination of transport    Group leader    SoMe

#### **EDUCATION**

2020-2022	Multimedia Design, Copenhagen School of Design and Technology    Front-end design and programming    User Experience (UX)       Content production    Busines    Technology
2016-2018	Communication courses, University of Southern Denmark     Corporate Communication    Multimodal tekstanalyse og - vurdering       Multimodal tekstforfatning    Kommunikations- og kampagneplanlægning       Organisation og kulturanalyse    Kommunikation i en globaliseret verden
2013-2016	BA, International Business Communication - English and media, University of Southern Denmark
2015	Erasmus exchange, Southampton Solent University (1 semester)

#### IT

12345	Adobe Photoshop, -Illustrator, and -InDesign
12345	frontend development in HTML, CSS and Javascript
12345	UX- and UI design
12345	SoMe

# **FREE TIME AND HOBBIES**

I love to be creative and often experiment with new projects and materials. I enjoy playing board games, cooking and every other weekend I play Dungeons and Dragons.